dialidol.com 2018-08-13

# DialIdol.com - Measuring the busy signal.

Your privacy is important to you, I know this because my privacy is important to me. As a result your privacy is important to DialIdol. DialIdol respects that you are trusting the application to run on your computer and doesn't collect any personal information. Here is what DialIdol collects and submits back to DialIdol.com

  * DialIdol tracks _who_ you attempted to vote for and whether that call resulted in a busy signal, error or timeout (vote). This information is submitted to DialIdol.com.
  * DialIdol notes the time difference between your computers clock and DialIdol.com's web server.
  * The version of DialIdol you are running.
  * Your network cards MAC address. The MAC address is used as a means to uniquely identify the results you are submitting. It is not associated with any other information.
  * Your area code is collected so that your results can be charted on the GeoPredictions map. Your area code is not associated with any other information.
  * If you choose to use DialIdol.com 's forums the information that your provide relating to your logon ID, name, email address, etc. will be collected. This information will be input by you and stored for your convenience on DialIdol.com's forum server. Your email address will be made public if you elect to allow people to send you email. Your first name and surname will be made public if you choose to provide that information. None of this information will be shared with anyone outside of DialIdol.com.

None of the above information can be traced back to you (by DialIdol & DialIdol.com or anyone else) without subpoenaing your ISP and translating your IP address to a name. DialIdol has no choice but to allow this to happen & if I did I'd prevent it.

At no time is any information that DialIdol & DialIdol.com collects shared with anyone or any thing.

DialIdol is not distributed with any other software so no other software can collect this information or jeopardize your privacy.

DialIdol & DialIdol.com does NOT know, search for, collect, track, trace or otherwise mine data other than what was disclosed in the above bullets. We especially do not collect any personal information.

In 2009 DialIdol introduced a new feature called YourPredictions. Any predictions that you make will be available for public consumption however that consumption will only trace back to your DialIdol ID, not your actual name. If you choose to divulge your actual name in DialIdol's YourPredictions/forum registration process you may also be choosing to disclose your name to the public and people may be able to search for you and any content you have submitted to DialIdol based on that information.

| 

 **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

Users may opt out of Interclick and other third party behavioral based advertising by visiting this URL :  
<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

; To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account by clicking Forums at the top of any page, entering their user name and password and clicking the profile link.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.dialidol.com/asp/TermsOfService/TOS.asp>

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [web site privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

http://www.dialidol.com

USA  
jrh7675@dialidol.com

This policy is powered by Trust Guard [PCI compliance](http://www.trust-guard.com/PCI-Compliance-s/65.htm) scans.
